Finding Aid for the Louis Thurston Nicholas Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Music/Book Catalogs
  - Sheet Music–Secular Songs (Box 318, Folder 12))
  - Sheet Music–Secular Choral Music (Box 318, Folder 13))
  - Sheet Music–Secular Octavos (both A Cappella and Accompanied) (Box 318, Folder 14))
  - Sheet Music–Secular Choral Music (Box 318, Folder 15))
  - Sheet Music–Secular Choral Music for mixed voices (Box 318, Folder 16))
  - Sheet Music–John Duke Songs (list included in this folder) (1) (Box 319, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music–John Duke Songs (2) (Box 319, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music–John Duke Songs (3) (Box 319, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music–John Duke Songs (4) (Box 319, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music–Contemporary American Songs (Box 319, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music–Contemporary American Songs–Ned Rorem and others (Box 319, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music–Songs–“5 American Folk Songs,” “4 Rhymes from Peacock Pie,” “4 Songs” by Samuel Barber; Mozart “Tell the Fair Ladies”; Contemporary American Songs (Box 319, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music–“Humorous Songs.” “A Song or Two then Silence”; “Four Negro Songs” “13 Additional Ways of Looking at a Blackbird’; “Prayer of Mary Queen of Scots” (Box 319, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music–Songs by E. Grieg, Tchaikovsky, Rachmaninoff (Box 319, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music–“The Curlew” by Peter Warlock for Tenor Voice, Flute, English Horn and String Quartet (Box 319, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music–British Songs (Box 319, Folder 11))
  - Sheet Music–Octavo–African American Spiritual Arrangements (Box 320, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music–African American Spiritual Arrangements (Box 320, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music —African American Spiritual Arrangements (Box 320, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music–Tenor Oratorio Repertoire (Box 320, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music–Handwritten (Box 320, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music–Songs in Manuscript (Box 320, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music–Songs in Manuscript (Box 320, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music–Maritana by W. Vincent Wallace (Box 320, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music–Climb Every Mountain; Williamson Music Inc. Choral Series; Tudor Church Music;; Agincourt Song; Liturgical Motets; Healey Willan; Sacred Songs Carl Fischer; Andalucia Suite Espagnol by Ernesto Lecuona (Box 320, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music–Strauss, Verdi, Ibert, Santoliquido (Box 320, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music–From a Lute of Jade–Gardner Read; Songs from “Calliope” (Box 320, Folder 11))
  - Sheet Music–American Songs–George Rochberg–2 Songs from “Tableaux” “Ballad” and “Nightpiece” (Box 320, Folder 12))
  - Sheet Music–Claudio Monteverdi–Selections from “L’Incoronazione di Poppea” and Ten Arias by A. Scarlatti (Box 320, Folder 13))
  - Sheet Music–Leonard Bernstein and other American Composers–Paul Bowles,Gena Branscombe, John Alden Carpenter, Elliott Carter (Box 321, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music–John Corighano, Joseph Fennimore, David Del Tredici (Box 321, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music–Cowell, Cumming, Dello Joio (Box 321, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music–William L. Dawson–Tuskegee Choir Series “The Rugged Yank” (Box 321, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music–David Diamond and Celius Dougherty (Box 321, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music–John Duke (Box 321, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music–The Rev. Mary Baker G. Eddy–Devotional Songs (Box 321, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music–John Edmunds–American Folk Songs; Henry Purcell-Songs (Box 321, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music–Victor Herbert (Box 321, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music–Songs by Gordon Myers, Charles Daginski, Sydney King Russell, Arthur Foote, Winifred Bury and others (Box 321, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music–Songs by H. Villa-Lobos; G. F. Handel, Umberto Giordano, Andrea Chenier; James Rogers and others (Box 321, Folder 11))
  - Sheet Music–Sweet Freedom’s Song by Robert Ward–Cantata for Chorus and Orchestra (Box 321, Folder 12))
  - Sheet Music–Bach, Handel, J. Strauss, Tchaikovsky, Guarnieri (Box 321, Folder 13))
  - Sheet Music–Songs by Laurie Gregory Nicholson, Ethelbert Nevin, Josephine McGill, Grace Mayhew, Mana-Zucca, Fritz Kreisler, A. Walter Kramer, Marshall Kernochan and others (Box 321, Folder 14))
  - Sheet Music–Songs by M. Wood Hill; Amy Woodforde Finden; George Maynard, and others (Box 321, Folder 15))
  - Sheet Music–Songs by H. Searle, Percy Grainger, John Duke, John Edmunds, Paul Bowles, Thomas Morley (Box 321, Folder 16))
  - Sheet Music—Serenade to Music by R. Vaughn Williams; The Resurrection from Liszt’s Christu (Box 322, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—Stabat Mater by Gioacchino Rossini (Box 322, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—Sextette from Lucia di Lammermoor; Quartet from Rigoletto (Box 322, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music—Messiah an Oratorio by G. F. Handel (Box 322, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music—Baroque Collections --Henry Purcell (Box 322, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music—Baroque Collections (Songs and Cantatas) by Bach, Purcell, Clerambault, Scarlatti, Handel, Vivaldi, etc. (Box 322, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music—Baroque Collections (Songs and Cantatas) Louis –Nicholas Clerambault—Orphee (Box 322, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music—Baroque Collections (Songs and Cantatas0—Italian Songs of the 18th Century (Box 322, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music—Operatic Collections and Arias—Les Plus Beaux Airs de L’Opera Francais by Gabriel Grovlez (Box 322, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music—Operatic Collections and Arias—Mozart, Bellini, Puccini, and others (Box 322, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music—Songs for Coloratura Voice (Box 322, Folder 11))
  - Sheet Music—Songs by Norman Dello Joio, David Diamond (Box 323, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Songs by Walter Golde, Harrison Kerr, Roger Sessions, Norman Dello Joio (Box 323, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Songs by Serge de Gastyne; Vittorio Giannini; John W. Work; Werner Singer; Albert Hay Malotte, John Sacco (Box 323, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music—Oxford University Press---Cock Robin by Howard Boatwright; The Water of Tyne; Yarmouth Fair; Two English Folksongs by R. Vaughan Williams; Three Old English Songs by Rebecca Clarke (Box 323, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music—Complimentary Copies of Secular Songs—Green is the Willow; Beneath a Southern Sky: A Christmas Song; Night and the Curtains Drawn and others (Box 323, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Songs—French, German, Spanish, Italian (Box 323, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music—Songs—Popular and Musicals (Box 323, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music—Glee and Chorus Book by J.E. Necollins (Box 323, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music—Church and Synagogue Music` (Box 323, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music—Vocal Solos for the Church Musician (Box 323, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music—Augsburg Choral Library (Box 323, Folder 11))
  - Sheet Music—Augsburg Choral Library (Box 323, Folder 12))
  - Sheet Music—Choral (Box 323, Folder 13))
  - Sheet Music—Transpositions (Box 323, Folder 14))
  - Sheet Music—Lists of Songs (Box 323, Folder 15))
  - Sheet Music--Songs (Box 323, Folder 16))
  - Sheet Music-Favorite Popular Songs—A-L (1) (Box 324, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—Favorite Popular Songs—A-L (2) (Box 324, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—Favorite Popular Songs—A-L (3) (Box 324, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music—Favorite Popular Songs—A-L (4) (Box 324, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music –Favorite Popular Songs—M- Z (1) (Box 324, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music—Favorite Popular Songs –M-Z (2) (Box 324, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music—Favorite Popular Songs—M-Z (3) (Box 324, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music—Songs from Motion Pictures A-N (Box 324, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music—Songs from Movies (Box 324, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music—Songs from Debussy and Italian Composers (Box 324, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music—Songs (including “Rounded up in Glory—A Cowboy Spiritual”) (Box 324, Folder 11))
  - Sheet Music—Songs—Sacred (Box 324, Folder 12))
  - Sheet Music—Songs (Box 324, Folder 13))
  - Sheet Music---Songs and Popular Ballads (Box 324, Folder 14))
  - Sheet Music—Choral Music (Box 325, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—Choral Music (Box 325, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—Choral Music (Box 325, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music—Choral Music (Box 325, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music—Choral Music (Box 325, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music—Choral—Anthems (Box 325, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music—Choral Music (Mostly from larger works—Persichetti, Rorem, Poulenc, Wagner, etc. (Box 325, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music—Choral Music Anthems for Church (Box 325, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music—Descants for Hymns (Box 325, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music—Hymns in Canon; Canons for Children; Hymns for Handbells (Box 325, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music—The Folk Song Sight Singing Series; Lead us, Lord, African Hymns; Singing Churchmen (Box 325, Folder 11))
  - Sheet Music—Introits for Festival and General Use; Voices of Worship; Hymnbook for Christian Worship (Box 325, Folder 12))
  - Sheet Music—Junior Musician (1963); The Church Musician (Oct. 1963) (Box 325, Folder 13))
  - Sheet Music—Scholin Choral Publications—Anthems—Sample copies (Box 325, Folder 14))
  - Sheet Music—General Anthems A Cappella Multi-Voiced (Box 326, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—General Anthems—A Cappella (Box 326, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—General Anthems—A Cappella (Box 326, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music—General Anthems—A Cappella (Box 326, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music—General Anthems—A Cappella (Box 326, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music—General Anthems—A Cappella (Box 326, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music—General Anthems—A Cappella (Box 326, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music—Easter Octavos—A Cappella and Accompanied (1) (Box 326, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music—Easter Octavos—A Cappella and Accompanied (2) (Box 326, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music---Easter Octavos—A Cappella and Accompanied (3) (Box 326, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music—Octavos for Palm Sunday and Easter (Box 327, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—Octavos for Lent, Palm Sunday and Easter (Box 327, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems for Lent and Holy Week, Easter (Box 327, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems for Lent And Easter (Box 327, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems for Lent and Easter (1962, 1964, 1965, H.W. Gray Co.) (Box 327, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems for Lent and Easter (1967,1969, 1970, H.W. Gray Co.) (Box 327, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems for Lent and Easter (Box 327, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred--Jewish (Box 327, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music—Octavos for Special Days (Box 327, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music—Octavos for Special Days (Box 327, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music—Octavos for Special Days (Box 327, Folder 11))
  - Sheet Music—Octavos for Special Days—Thanksgiving, Pentecost (Box 328, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—Octavos for Special Days—New Year; Patriotic Praise of Peace; Thanksgiving (Box 328, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—Octavos for Special Days—Communion; Harvest; Marriage; Memorial Day; Mission (Box 328, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music—Octavos for Special Days—All Saints Day; Brotherhood; Communion (Box 328, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 328, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music—Choral –Sacred—Isaac Watts Contemplates the Cross A Choral Cycle by John W. Work (Box 328, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music—Choral—Sacred (The Choir Leader, The Anthem Folio) (Box 328, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music—Choral Music—Sacred (Box 328, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 328, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 328, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 328, Folder 11))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Octavos for Women’s Voices (Box 329, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Octavos for Women’s Voices (Box 329, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Octavos for Women’s Voices (Box 329, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos for Women’s Voices (Box 329, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos for Women’s Voices (Box 329, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos for Women’s Voices (Box 329, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos for Women’s Voices, 4 part and 5 part (Box 329, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos,for Women’s Voices, 4 part and 5 part (Box 329, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos for Women’s Voices (Box 329, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music—Three part songs for Women’s Voices (Box 329, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music—Opera Airs for Young Women; Opera Airs for Young Men (Box 329, Folder 11))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos for Male Voices (Box 330, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos for Male Voices (Box 330, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos for Male Voices (Box 330, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos for Male Voices (Box 330, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos for Male Voices (Box 330, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Octavos for Male Voices (Box 330, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos (Box 330, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos (Box 330, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos (Box 330, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos (Box 330, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos (Box 330, Folder 11))
  - Sheet Music—Secular Octavos—Unison (Some with optional instruments) (Box 330, Folder 12))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 331, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 331, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 331, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 331, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 331, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 331, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 331, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 331, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 331, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 331, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems-Sacred (Box 332, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems-Sacred (Box 332, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 332, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 332, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Sacred (Box 332, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems-Sacred (Box 332, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music— Anthems--Choral—Sacred (Box 332, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems--Choral –Sacred (Box 332, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems--Choral—Sacred (Box 332, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems--Choral—Sacred (Box 332, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music— Anthems—Choral—Sacred (Box 332, Folder 11))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems-Choral—Sacred (Box 332, Folder 12))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Choral—Sacred (Box 332, Folder 13))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems—Choral—Sacred (Box 332, Folder 14))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Unison Octavos (Some with optional instruments) (Box 333, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Unison Octavos (Some with optional instruments) (Box 333, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Octavos (Box 333, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Octavos (Box 333, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Choral Anthems (Box 333, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred (Box 333, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred (Box 333, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred (Box 333, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred music (Box 333, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music--Sacred (Box 333, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Choral Music (Box 334, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Choral Music (Box 334, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Choral Music (Box 334, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Octavo Choruses for Mixed Voices (Box 334, Folder 4))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred—Anthems (Box 334, Folder 5))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred –Anthems (Box 334, Folder 6))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred –Anthems (Box 334, Folder 7))
  - Sheet Music—Anthems (Box 334, Folder 8))
  - Sheet Music--Anthems (Box 334, Folder 9))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Songs (Box 334, Folder 10))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Songs (Box 334, Folder 11))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Songs (Box 334, Folder 12))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Songs (Box 334, Folder 13))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Music (Box 334, Folder 14))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Solos and Collections—The Church Year in Song—A Collection of Religious Songs (Box 334, Folder 15))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Solos and Collections (Box 334, Folder 16))
  - Sheet Music—Sacred Solos and Collections (Box 334, Folder 17))
  - Sheet Music—Ernest Chausson—Concert en Re Majeur, opus 21 (Box 335, Folder 1))
  - Sheet Music—Elizabeth Gest Series and others (Box 335, Folder 2))
  - Sheet Music—Morton Gould; Camille Saint-Saens and others (Box 335, Folder 3))
  - Sheet Music (Box 335, Folder 4))
  - Philip Glass—Three Choruses for Mixed Voices with texts by Carl Sandburg—1965 (Box 336, Folder 1))
  - “The Holy City”; “Like as the Hart Desireth”; “The Lord is My Light” (Box 336, Folder 2))
  - “My Task”; J.S. Bach’s Jesu Joy of Man’s Desiring; Sheep May Safely Graze; “O Perfect Love”; Out of the Deep; I will Lift up Mine Eyes unto the Hills; When Jesus Wept; Hashkivenu (Box 336, Folder 3))
  - “I See His Blood upon the Rose”; Psalm XXIII by Paul Creston; Thanks be to God; Goin’ Home; “I Shall Not Pass Again this Way”; The Choir Leader (Box 336, Folder 4))
  - “Leave It with Him”; “The Palms”; “Beautiful Isle of Somewhere”; “O Lord Most Holy” (Box 336, Folder 5))
  - “Entreat Me Not to Leave Thee”; “There is a Green Hill Far Away”; “Blessed Be Thou Lord God of Israel”; “Christ Went up into the Hills”; “God Shall Wipe Away all Tears” (Box 336, Folder 6))
  - “These Sacred Songs”; “How Beautiful Upon the Mountains”; “O Leave Your Sheep”; Songs by Sidney (Box 336, Folder 7))
  - “Prayer”; “Halleluia”; “They Shall Run and Not be Weary”; “The Lord’s Prayer”; the 23rd Psalm” (Box 336, Folder 8))
  - “ I walked today where Jesus walked”; “The Living God”; “There is No Death”; “Lord Jesus think on me”; “How Long will thou forget me?”; “Great Peace Have They that love the Law”; Devotional Songs by Mary Baker Eddy; “A Psalm of Praise “ by Ned Rorem (Box 336, Folder 9))
  - “Ave Maria”; “Jesus Only”; “Angels Roll the Rock Away”; “Just for Today”; “Upon a Hill”; “The Publican” (Box 336, Folder 10))
  - “Ward-Stephens Musical Settings”; “The Cross”; “Perfect Love”; “How Beautiful on the Mountains”; “Gesu Bambino”; “A Hymn of Thanksgiving” (Box 336, Folder 11))
  - “Gloria”; “Rose of My Heart”; “Indian Songs”; “Folklore Series; “Song to the Moon” by Dvorak (Box 336, Folder 12))
  - “Georgia Sleep Song”; “Whispering Rose”; “I Searched the World for You”; “The Joy of Living”; “When you are near”; “The Daisy’s Secret” (Box 336, Folder 13))
  - “Les Pecheurs de Perles”; “O Lord of all Creation”; “What Child is This”; “The Dream Waltz”; “Sonate” (Box 336, Folder 14))
  - “March from Aida”; Hey Diddle Diddle; “What Tongue Can Tell Thy Greatness Lord?’; “Singing Time to Sleep”; etc. (Box 336, Folder 15))
  - “The Infinite Shining Heavens” and other (Box 336, Folder 16))
  - “BL-ND and P-G”; “ Keep Your Foot on the Soft Pedal”; etc. (Box 336, Folder 17))
  - “Beets and Turnips Fox Trot”; “In the Eye there lies the Heart”; “Beloved it is Morn”; “He Sent Me You”; “Mignon”; “Indian Love Call”; “Slumber Boat” (Box 336, Folder 18))
  - “For Old Bombay”; “In a Persian Garden”; “Who Shall be Fairest”; “The Rosary”; others (Box 336, Folder 19))
  - “A Perfect Day”; Cancao de Saudade by Villa-Lobos; others (Box 336, Folder 20))
  - Music/ Book Catalogs (Box 337, Folder 1))
  - Music/ Book Catalogs (Box 337, Folder 2))
  - Music Catalog—Hathaway and Bowers Automatic Musical Instruments, catalogue No.7, November 1968 (Box 337, Folder 3))
  - Music Catalogs—Oxford Vocal Music; Oxford Choral Music 1968; Oxford Music Bulletin, 1965 (Box 337, Folder 4))
  - Music Catalogs—Choral Works (Box 337, Folder 5))
  - Music Catalogs—from Oxford and Mills Music (Box 337, Folder 6))
  - Music Catalogs (Box 337, Folder 7))
  - Music Catalogs (Box 337, Folder 8))
  - Music Catalogs—Arno Press, Belwin Mills, American Composers Alliance, Books on Music (Box 337, Folder 9))
  - Music Catalogs—Crescendo, Da Capo Press; Greenwood Press; Harvard University Press; Music Exchange (Box 337, Folder 10))
  - Music Catalogs—Norton; Cooper Square Publishers; University of California; and others (Box 337, Folder 11))
  - Music/ Book Catalogs (Box 337, Folder 12))
  - Music/ Book Catalogs (Box 337, Folder 13))
  - Vocal Music Catalogue (Box 337, Folder 14))
  - Lists of Music—History of Musical Theater; Operas and Opera Arias; other songs (Box 338, Folder 1))
  - Music Catalogs—Broadman Music, 1965-1966 (Box 338, Folder 2))
  - Music Catalog—Duo-Art Piano Music (Box 338, Folder 3))
  - Music Catalog—Duo-Art Dance Music (Box 338, Folder 4))
  - Music Catalog—Hal Leonard Vocal Music Catalog, 2001 (Box 338, Folder 5))
  - Music Catalog—Arrow Music Press, (1948?) (Box 338, Folder 6))
  - Music Catalog—Augsburg Collection of Sacred Music—Choir Director’s Guide (Box 338, Folder 7))
  - Music Catalogs—Westminster Hi-Fi, 1957-1958 (Box 338, Folder 8))
  - Record Catalogs—Columbia—New Process Records; Victor Records (Box 338, Folder 9))
  - Music/Book Catalogs—Opera (Box 338, Folder 10))
  - Music Catalogs (Box 338, Folder 11))
  - Music Catalogs (Box 338, Folder 12))
  - Music Catalogs (Box 338, Folder 13))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 338, Folder 14))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 338, Folder 15))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 339, Folder 1))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 339, Folder 2))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 339, Folder 3))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 339, Folder 4))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 339, Folder 5))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 339, Folder 6))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 339, Folder 7))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 339, Folder 8))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 339, Folder 9))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 339, Folder 10))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 340, Folder 1))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 340, Folder 2))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 340, Folder 3))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 340, Folder 4))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 340, Folder 5))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 340, Folder 6))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 340, Folder 7))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 340, Folder 8))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 340, Folder 9))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 340, Folder 10))
  - Music/Book Catalogs (Box 340, Folder 11))
- PROMOTIONAL MATERIALS AND PRESS RELEASES
  - Coolidge and Krisofferson, National Geographic and others with photographs (Box 341, Folder 1))
  - Erica Morini—Zvi Zeitlin (and other play events) (Box 341, Folder 2))
  - Mischa Elman—Frances Magnes (Box 341, Folder 3))
  - Frederic Balazs—John Dalley—Dichter (Box 341, Folder 4))
  - Air Force Band—Juilliard Quartet—Warsaw String Quartet (Box 341, Folder 5))
  - Albeneri Trio—Zurich Chamber Orchestra (Box 341, Folder 6))
  - American Ballet Theatre—Pilobolus Dance Theatre (Box 341, Folder 7))
  - Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre—Douglas Williams (Box 341, Folder 8))
  - Newsletter—The Ford Foundation, July 6, 1966—March 2, 1969 (Box 341, Folder 9))
  - Newsletter—The Ford Foundation, Jan. 2, 1970—March 7, 1971 (Box 341, Folder 10))
  - Newsletter—The Ford Foundation Letter, October 15, 1971—December 15, 1973 (Box 341, Folder 11))
  - Newsletter—The Ford Foundation, sFeb. 1, 1974—April 1, 1975 (Box 341, Folder 12))
  - Newsletter—The Ford Foundation, March 9, 1959—Dec. 16, 1963 (Box 341, Folder 13))
  - Group Attractions that have Appeared in Nashville—American Ballet Theatre—Chattanooga Symphony Orchestra (Box 342, Folder 1))
  - Group Attractions that have Appeared in Nashville—Claremont College—Howard A Cappella Choir (Box 342, Folder 2))
  - Group Attractions that have Appeared in Nashville—Lamoureux Orchestra of Paris—New York String Sextet (Box 342, Folder 3))
  - Group Attractions that have Appeared in Nashville—Oberlin Wind Ensemble—Fred Waring (Box 342, Folder 4))
  - Local/ Nashville Concerts (Box 342, Folder 5))
  - Chattanooga; Dallas Symphony; Naples, Florida Symphony; Music at University of Connecticut; Musicians Club of Evansville (Box 342, Folder 6))
  - New York Philomusica—Virtuosi Sinfonietta (Box 342, Folder 7))
  - Guide to National Symphony (1962-63 Season); Saint Louis Symphony; 4 Operas by Buren Schryock on the Origin of the American Indian; New Orleans Opera, 1972-1973 (Box 342, Folder 8))
  - Hartford Chamber Orchestra—Lucerne Festival Strings (Box 342, Folder 9))
  - Clark Angel, Concert Organist; Edward Brewer. Harpsichordist; Xavier Darasse, organ; Virgil Fox, Donald McDonald; Pierre Cochereau; Karl Richter; et. al. (Box 342, Folder 10))